( grunts )
I 'm sorry .
- Oh , it 's okay . - I 'm sorry , baby .
- I 'm sorry . - Fucking shoulder .
Keep going .
That 's helping .
Never .
Just a little bit . Just to clean it up .
I 'm not cutting it .
But you 'd look so hot with short hair .
- Oh , would I ? - Yeah .
- Thank you . - ( chuckles ) No , no , no ...
Sorry , I didn 't mean it like that .
You are hot .
You are the hottest .
- Keep going . - You and your gorgeous ,
thick , long hair .
- Continue ... - I just fucking love the way it 's long .
Yeah ?
Happy Father 's Day , Daddy !
Kids , we said after breakfast .
I want cake for breakfast .
Wow ! Chocolate with sprinkles !
My favorite .
Happy Father 's Day !
- Open it ! Open it ! Open it ! - Open it ! Open it ! Open it !
I am , I am .
I like building up the anticipation .
Oh , you guys ...
- You like it ? - I love it .
Muah ! I love it .
- Thank you . - Mom helped us .
No , I didn 't . It was all their idea .
- Right , kids ? - ( both ) Right .
- Cake ! Cake ! Cake ! - Cake ! Cake ! Cake !
- Okay , okay . - Cake ! Cake ! Cake !
Cake ! Cake ! Cake ! Cake !
Oh , look at that beautiful looking cake !
- ( screams ) - Ah ...
Who did this to monster !
- ( grunting ) - ( shrieking )
( chuckles )
Oh , you can 't hide from monster !
Monster can smell you !
( Jake ) Run ! Run ! Monster 's coming !
- ( growling ) - ( Lisa squealing )
Argh !
Monster made kids disappear .
And ...
Monster wanna finish what we started .
Too late , the kids are awake .
Monster sad .
I 'm sure monster can wait till Monday .
Monster been waiting three weeks .
Yeah , but with the kids and my exhibition
I cannot keep everybody happy all the time .
Whoa , whoa , whoa ! Whoa , whoa , whoa !
Monster doesn 't want to start a fight .
Okay . Sorry , me neither .
I promise we 'll finish this as soon as I get back .
Oh , monster happy .
- Monster happy . - ( giggling )
Monster very happy .
- ( growling ) - ( children laughing )
( speaking Spanish )
Yeah , Mommy .
- Gracias . - De nada .
- Everybody packed ? - Yeah .
Monkey , good boy .
Dad , why can 't we take Monkey to the beach with us ?
Yeah , you know he loves the beach .
Monkey needs to stay here and keep your dad company
so he doesn 't stay all alone during the weekend .
- That 's unfair . - Knock-knock .
( kids ) Hey , Louis !
Hey , guys , hot off the presses .
( speaking Spanish )
- What 's going on , Louis ? - What 's shakin ' ?
What 's going on , little guys ?
Mr. Webber , how are you , sir ?
Morning , Louis .
I 'd offer you a hand , but all I can lift is this coffee .
Oh , that 's what happens when you try to impress girls in the bat cage .
I wasn 't flirting , I was being a gentleman .
Yeah , I 'm sure she was a poor helpless 25-year-old .
Yeah , helpless .
( Karen chuckles )
Do you know what this is ?
Is it a Father 's Day present for Daddy ?
No . No , this is Mommy 's catalog .
Assuming they got the color right this time .
Oh , let 's hope .
( Lisa ) I think they did .
( speaking Spanish )
It 's a little bit magenta , but it 's almost perfect .
- What 's magenta ? - This color .
Honey , it 's perfect .
Mom , can Louis come to the beach with us ?
Yeah .
No , Louis needs to stay here and do some work .
Just like your daddy .
That 's correct .
I have to come back with all the alcohol for the super-secret
Father 's Day party that me and your dad are gonna have tonight .
Louis ! Shh !
- Oh , come on . - You 're not having a party .
I 'm not having a party ,
I 'm working very hard .
Did you pack your gun ?
- ( both ) Yes . - Did you pack the bomb ?
- Yes . - Have you packed the cannon ?
- ( Jake ) Yes . - Have you packed the chainsaw ?
You didn 't pack the chainsaw ?
Go get the chainsaw , man !
The cement still hasn 't dried , but it should be fine by tomorrow night .
Okay .
Still , it 's extremely fragile and I don 't trust those movers
after the mess they made at the gallery .
Mmm-mmm . No , I 'll take care of it . Don 't worry .
Okay , gracias , I 'll have it all packed up for you .
Okay .
It 's almost dry though .
Yeah , so I 'll just text you when it 's at the gallery .
Don 't worry about anything ,
I got it all under control . You have a good weekend at the beach .
Enjoy yourself . I 'm out .
Gracias , Louis .
- Mr. Webber , I 'll see you tomorrow . - Thank you .
I mean , " tonight " for the super-secret party .
- Louis ... - See you , kids .
- Bye , Louis . - Super-secret party ?
- Super-secret party . - Okay .
Is this the last one ?
- You like it ? - I love it .
- Good . - I think it should be bigger .
- ( chuckles ) You think so ? - Yeah , then we can get the pool .
Okay , I 'll do it bigger next time .
I told Vivian tomorrow at 2 : 00 .
I don 't need her therapy anymore , it 's healing .
Tell that to your shoulder .
Dad , are you sure you can 't come to the beach with us ?
I would love nothing more , sport .
But if Daddy doesn 't work this weekend , we 'll have to live in a box .
Do you guys want to live in a box ?
- No . - No . Not really .
Me neither . Unless I designed it .
Okay , say goodbye to Daddy .
Bye , Daddy .
Say goodbye to Monkey .
( both ) Bye , Monkey .
Daddy , don 't forget to send all your party pix on Instagram .
Okay .
Call me when you get there .
I will . I love you .
- I love you . - I love you .
Bye , guys .
- Bye . - Bye , Daddy .
( Jake ) Get a haircut , Dad !
Well , Monkey ...
Looks like it 's just me and you , kid .
( thunder rumbling )
( rock music playing )
( phone ringing )
( music stops )
Hey , baby .
How 's the house ?
Hi ! It 's perfect .
Look . Kids , say hello to your dad .
- ( both ) Hi ! - Hello .
All it needs is you .
- I love you . - I love you , too .
Miss you .
Good night .
( turns music on )
( knocking at door )
( music stops )
( barks )
( knocking continues )
Who 's there ?
( girl ) Just one second , sir , please .
- Hello ? - Could I use your phone , please ?
Yes ?
We 're so sorry to bother you , sir ,
but could you please tell us where the Gregorys live ?
This is the third house we 've tried .
Looks like everyone 's gone for the long weekend .
The Gregorys ?
No , I don 't know anyone around here
by that name .
What 's the address ?
Um ,
I honestly don 't know .
My phone got wet and she left hers at her house .
The taxi just dropped us here . We 've been walking around for , like , 20 minutes .
Yeah , my feet are , like , dying .
Well , I 'm sorry . I 'm afraid I can 't help you .
* Bless you .
( giggles )
Here .
Thank you .
Well , if you guys want you can come in and use my phone .
Oh , thanks , but ...
All our contacts are on our phones .
I ... I don 't even know my own number , can you believe it ?
Maybe Ashley 's on Facebook chat ?
Ah , genius .
Actually , would you mind if we just used your computer for a sec ?
We don 't want to impose .
We 'll just get the address and be out of your hair .
Yeah . Sure .
Come in .
Thank you .
( thunder rumbling )
( girls giggling )
No , it 's fine . Don 't worry .
Oh , I don 't mind .
We don 't want to mess up your house .
Yeah . Excuse me .
Um , thank you so , so much .
- I know this is so random . - It 's fine .
Hang on , I 'll get you an iPad and some towels .
Thanks .
( girl ) Nice house .
Girls ?
( both ) We 're in here .
I 'm so sorry , it was warmer here .
Hope you don 't mind .
We were freezing .
Here .
Oh , my God . Thank you .
This is beyond embarrassing .
Don 't worry about it .
Make yourselves at home .
I 'm Bel , by the way .
Evan .
- Nice to meet you . - Nice to meet you .
Ashley 's online .
Cool .
You 're a life saver , Evan .
Not everyone would just let two total strangers into their house these days .
Well , you don 't look that dangerous .
Worst case scenario ,
I know I can take the both of you .
I 'm not so sure .
I do air boxing .
- Air boxing ? - Yeah , like , you know ?
- Oh , okay . - Oh , my God , I 'm sorry .
- Excuse me , sir . - Yes .
- What 's the address ? - His name 's Evan .
Evan ?
458 Canter .
Wow . We 're like , far .
It was Kantner , not Canter .
The cab must 've misunderstood us .
I told you that he was going the wrong way .
That guy barely spoke English .
I mean , his English was worse than mine .
This is so retarded .
Don 't worry about it . I 'll call an Uber .
No . No , no , no .
We can find a cab outside . It 's no problem .
Not around here , you won 't .
Trust me , it 's the only reliable way .
You sure ? I feel like such an idiot .
We don 't want to ruin your night .
No really . It 's fine .
It 's looking for a driver .
And it 'll be here in ...
45 minutes .
That long ?
The rain .
We 're lucky we even got one .
( whispering indistinctly )
What ?
( giggling )
Um , I know this is gonna sound weird ,
but could we maybe throw our clothes in your dryerjust for , like , 10 minutes ?
We really don 't want to go to a party soaking wet .
( Bel ) No .
Please ?
Sure , sure . Um ...
We have some extra robes . I 'll , uh , go get them .
- Thank you . - Yay .
This is literally saving our lives .
Yeah , we could get sick and die .
( both giggling )
You have your phone ?
Uh yeah , why ?
I can try and fix it .
Really ? Oh .
My kid dropped mine in the tub ,
and you won 't believe this , but if you put it in rice
it kinda dries it out .
- That would be awesome . - Rice ?
Oh , my God , you 're like a MythBuster .
Thank you so much , Evan .
You 're welcome ...
- Genesis . - Genesis .
Yeah , like the beginning of time .
In the beginning .
- ( chuckles ) - Sorry .
Yup , that was ... You 're sick of that .
Thanks .
I 'll , uh ...
I 'll go get you some .
( Kettle whistling )
Hey , Evan ?
Where should we put these ?
Oh , I 'll take them .
No , we can do it . We don 't mind .
I got it .
I made you some tea .
- Thank you . - Thank you , that 's nice .
- So sweet . - I 'll trade you .
Uh , okay .
Gracias .
Excuse me .
( dryer spinning )
( girls giggling in distance )
( Bel ) Oh , my God .
( Monkey barking )
( Bel ) Oh , sorry .
We were trying to warm up .
Yeah , I mean , we 've never seen one of these before .
- A real one . - It 's okay .
Just be careful . It 's old .
I see you 've met Monkey .
Yeah , this is Monkey .
It 's time for Monkey to go to bed .
- Bye , Monkey . - Night-night , Monkey .
- Night-night . - Sweet dreams .
Bye , Monkey .
All right , Monkey .
Go home , Monkey .
You have so many records .
Sorry . We had to try one .
Stop apologizing , it 's okay .
I love this album . You have good taste .
This is like ...
An insane collection .
- Yeah . - It must be worth a fortune .
Well , everything 's online now , so ...
But , uh , I love the sound of vinyl .
You 're really into music .
Well , it used to be myjob .
What ? Like a record salesman ?
- ( giggling ) - I was a DJ .
Oh , my God . That 's so cool !
You 're like Major Lazer !
It was in my 20s .
It 's really a hobby now , I haven 't had a real gig in years .
Wait , how old are you ?
I 'm 43 .
- No fucking way . - I can 't believe you 're 43 .
I thought you were , like , 28 or 30 at the most .
Well , I got married when I was 30 .
Where 's your wife ?
She 's at the beach with my kids .
We were gonna spend Father 's Day there , but , uh , work happened .
Oh , my God , you are all alone on Father 's Day .
Poor Evan , we 'll keep you company !
( both ) Hugs !
No , it 's fine . We celebrated this morning .
Whoa , you 're not 43 .
You must work out , like , every day .
Yeah , I keep in shape .
Not like when I was in my 20s , but , uh ...
Come on , any guy that ripped
is more into his own ass than yours .
Yeah , I mean , like , seriously ,
is that all you do ?
Oh , my God ,
I remember I fucked this model once ,
and while we were having sex
I caught him doing crunches in the mirror .
- ( chuckles ) - It was the gayest thing ever .
I 'd take somebody that 's older and more experienced
over an Abercrombie model any day .
( Genesis ) Yeah .
( thunder rumbling )
Well , hopefully one day you 'll find both .
I don 't know .
Underwear models are the kind of guys you fuck when you 're 14 .
That 's a statement .
- This is your wife ? - Yup .
( Bel ) I want to see it .
Wow ! She 's so pretty .
She 's beautiful . You 're a lucky guy .
Yeah , I certainly am .
I 'm just an architect , but , uh ,
she 's the real deal .
Most of what you see is hers .
- She made all these ? - Yeah .
( Genesis ) Wow .
They 're so pretty .
I love these colors .
Red 's my favorite .
This is amazing .
I actually studied art history .
I 'm no expert , I was only there for a semester , but ,
this ...
This is like a Gaudi building , but small .
Yeah , my wife loves Gaudi .
She was , uh , she was born in Barcelona .
( Bel ) Like me ?
( speaking Spanish )
English , English . You guys sound too sexy .
That 's about the extent of my Spanish anyway .
My kids speak it perfectly .
Your wife 's an amazing artist .
Why are these sculptures here ?
They should be in like , MOMA .
Actually , um ...
It 's not exactly MOMA ...
But she 's having a big gallery show in LA .
Karen Alvarado . That 's such a pretty name .
An architect and an artist .
You guys are like the perfect couple .
And she 's so hot .
You must have sex , like , all day .
- Bel ! - What ?
I would .
That 's Belly for you .
She sees a hot girl and chases after her .
Well , it 's okay . I have no complaints .
Sorry , I was just being honest .
No , no . It 's fine .
Um , but , uh ...
I must say
I 'm not used to girls just being so open about that .
About what ?
Sex ?
No , I mean ... Yes .
- Yeah . - Yes .
It 's just sex .
Right .
Now you seem old .
Sorry . So sorry .
Twenty minutes away .
How long have you and your wife been together ?
I was 29 and she was 20 .
It 's been awhile .
So you haven 't been with anyone else in all those years ?
Fourteen years , nope .
Wow .
How is that even possible ?
Well , when you love someone ...
( Genesis ) Come on , Evan .
Humans are the only species that practice monogamy .
I mean , we 're animals . We 're more animals than animals .
It 's in our DNA .
Like , being with one person your whole life ,
is going against your own nature .
Look .
It 's like this .
I understand men .
I know whenever I get married ,
my husband is gonna want to be with other girls .
So , I want to get comfortable with having threesomes now ,
because I know that 's the only way he 'll never cheat on me .
( laughs nervously )
Wow .
( Evan laughs )
So , are you guys ... What do you guys do ?
I mean , are you ... Are you in school or something ?
I mean ...
Actually , we 're flight attendants .
Really ?
What would you like for your entree , sir ?
We have chicken ...
And pasta .
( speaking Spanish )
Please buckle your seatbelt , sir .
We may be encountering some turbulence .
( speaking Spanish )
( Evan ) So ...
Where you guys based out of ?
( sighs ) Everywhere .
Last weekend we were in New Zealand for 24 hours .
It was awesome .
Wow , how was that jet lag ?
We don 't sleep .
( Genesis ) It 's like being a fake rock star .
You know , you fly around the world first class ,
drinks are on the house and they pay you for it .
I 'm jealous .
I once got offered a tour when I was a DJ .
Not like you guys , but , uh , Tri-State area .
Yeah , well , I think traveling is the best way to get life experience .
Especially when you 're only there for 24 hours .
You really make the most of it .
( Genesis ) Yeah , we make the most of it .
Unlike that fucking starfish we work with . Ugh .
( Bel , softly ) ) Ugh , starfish .
- Starfish ? - This girl we work with ...
She doesn 't have to do anything in bed ,
she just lies there like a fucking starfish .
Hence , starfish .
I mean , who 'd want to fuck that ?
- ( chuckles ) - ( Bel ) I don 't understand girls like that .
When I 'm with a guy , I want him to have the time of his life .
- No rules . - None .
Nothing 's off limit , sexually .
Sex with boundaries isn 't really sex .
If our bodies are capable of doing it ,
then we were meant to . Right ?
( thunder cracking )
Oh , Evan ? Can I use your bathroom ?
Of course . It 's , uh , down the hall on the right .
Thanks .
I don 't know any of these .
Well , I have pretty eclectic taste .
You have Spanish music .
Chilean , actually .
My wife loves her , Fran Valenzuela .
Can you put it on ?
Sure .
She 's really talented .
She started composing when she was 13 .
This is her third album .
( music playing )
( speaking Spanish )
Wow !
How did you know that would mix ?
DJ 'ing is like mixing a drink .
First you find the right ingredients ,
then you find the blend .
Evan , I have something to confess .
Yes ?
I 'm glad we knocked on your door .
I 'm having a way better time here
then at that stupid party we were supposed to go to .
Well , I have to confess , it 's not usually this exciting around here
at 1 : 30 in the morning .
It 's like destiny that we were meant to meet .
Do you believe in destiny , Evan ?
I 'm an architect .
So obviously I believe that things happen by your own design .
Well , I do .
I don 't think people just meet randomly .
I think that if we are here , together ,
it 's because
there 's something we have to learn from each other .
Discover .
( cell phone vibrating )
It 's here .
I 'll go get Genesis .
I 'll get your clothes .
What the fuck !
Guys !
Guys , the car 's outside .
Guys , I have your clothes , they 're pretty much dry .
( giggling )
- Guys ! - ( giggling )
All right , I 'm coming in ,
I 'm not looking , so excuse me .
- Surprise ! - Surprise !
What the fuck are you doing ?
- Come on , Evan . Join us . - Yeah , join the party .
- Come here . - The car 's outside .
The car can wait . Come on .
I 'm gonna tell the driver that you 're coming out .
Get dressed . Now .
Please . Here 's your clothes .
Evan . Look at us .
Come on ...
Whoa , whoa , whoa . Stop . Stop . Stop .
I can 't do this . I 'm married .
Happily . Okay ?
Yes . You can .
Hey , it 's our little secret .
Whoa , stop . Stop .
It 's just sex . We 're all adults here .
I 'm flattered .
But really , I can 't . Please , get dressed .
- ( giggling ) - Yeah , you can .
Come on , just one day .
Just relax and enjoy it .
You like this ?
Have you ever had two girls do this to you before ?
( moaning )
- Happy Father 's Day ! - Happy Father 's Day !
( phone vibrating )
( mumbling )
( girls laughing )
( BOTH LAUGHING )
( Announcer on TV ) It 's time for the Family Feud !
Introducing the Levy family !
- Morning , Daddy . - Evan ! Evan !
Watch this !
( both shrieking )
Belly ! Belly ! Catch ! Catch !
( Announcer on T continues )
- Sorry , Belly . - ( laughing )
I thought you guys left .
- We made you breakky . - I 'm not hungry .
Monkey , that 's mine .
And the star of Family Feud , Richard Dawson !
You two live together ?
Yeah .
Where ?
Why , Evan ?
So I can drive you there .
I haven 't been home in like four years .
This could be our home .
I 'll drive you wherever you want .
( laughing )
Did I say something funny ?
Mmm-hmm .
I want to go to Paris , Evan .
No , let 's go to Tokyo .
- London . - ( laughter )
- Rome . - ( giggling )
( cell phone ringing )
( speaking Spanish )
Don 't let your breakky get cold .
( phone ringing )
Hey , baby .
( Karen ) Hey , you 're alive .
Yeah , ah , barely .
I forgot how strong Vanessa 's weed was .
I just woke up .
You are such a lightweight .
- How are the kids ? - Not so good .
- What happened ? - ( both ) Evan !
Jake got stung by a jellyfish . He was crying .
- Oh , no ! - Yeah .
Poor little guy .
- He 's okay now . - Where is he ?
He 's back at the beach .
It was a little bit hairy for a while ,
but now he 's okay .
What about you ? How 's your project ?
Great . Great . Great .
Uh , I 'm in a really good groove now ,
so , home stretch .
Okay , then don 't let me interrupt you .
Let 's talk later . You seem a little distracted .
No . That 's not what I meant .
It 's just ...
I just want to finish
so I don 't have to think about it , you know ?
Maybe if I get done early , I can ,
I can drive out there .
Baby , I get it . Don 't stress .
Do what you have to do .
- I love you . - Love you , too .
Don 't smoke all our weed .
I won 't . I promise .
- Bye . - Ciao .
Shit ! Shit ! Shit !
Are you hungry now ?
Get up ! And get dressed !
Right now !
Excuse me , sir . Can you tell me where Evan is ?
You know , that sweet guy that saved two girls from the rain ?
He 's gone . Get the fuck up .
Let 's go .
I don 't appreciate your tone of voice .
Go !
Come on , Belly . Looks like Evan lost his sense of humor .
- Go ! - ( laughing )
Hello !
Let 's go !
Where 's Bel ?
I don 't know , she 's not my friend .
Bel !
Bel ?
( blows party horn )
- ( laughing ) - What the fuck are you doing ?
You tell us to get dressed .
Come on . Playtime 's over .
Evan , can you hold me ?
Please , just once more .
- Please , I miss your hugs . - Bel . Listen to me .
You 're leaving . Now .
Get dressed .
- I love you . - Bel ...
- I love you . - No !
I love you so much .
God damn it ! Fuck !
I love you . I can 't help it .
( mumbling )
I 'm crazy about you .
( panting )
( screaming )
You have three minutes !
I 'll be outside !
Get dressed !
Let 's go !
What in the fuck are you doing !
You have any idea what you 've done ?
Yeah . It 's called art .
We were inspired from last night . Remember ?
I 'm calling the fucking police .
- Go ahead . - ( dialing number )
What the fuck is so funny !
I just have a funny story for them .
It 's called " To Catch a Predator . "
What the fuck are you talking about ?
Fifteen to 20 years ?
I think it is 20 .
Fifteen gets you 20 , right ?
- I don 't believe it . - You don 't have to .
The jury will .
Statutory rape , Evan .
Twenty years behind bars .
And that 's just for one of us .
And I 'm not planning on taking a shower .
I have evidence .
Really ?
So how could you be a flight attendant if you 're only 15 ?
( both laughing )
What the fuck ! What ?
We saw that in a movie , Evan .
I told you he 'd believe it .
Do you want to check my ID ?
She doesn 't have one , she 's too young .
Okay .
What do you want ?
We want to make breakky for you every morning .
Come on .
Just tell me . How much do you want ?
Don 't be mad , Evan .
That 's not you .
- You 're different from the others . - Yeah .
How much !
What do you think we are , hookers ?
Jesus , Evan , we 're not fucking whores !
Yeah .
You 're the fucking whore !
Whore !
( doorbell ringing ) ( Vivian ) Evan ?
It 's Vivian !
Do not move !
Evan !
Evan , I 'm so sorry I 'm late ,
but that storm blew branches out all over town .
It even knocked two traffic lights out .
I swear , I swear I was sitting there for 15 minutes
and I was trying to navigate , but there was repair trucks .
It 's fine . It 's fine .
Actually , I 'm feeling much better .
Oh , then that 's really good because then this 'll help .
I 'll give you a relaxation massage , it 'll help circulate .
Actually ... Karen should have told you ,
I have a lot of work to do this weekend .
I love Karen . I love her so much , how is she ?
She is so talented .
I cannot wait to see her exhibition .
In fact , you know what ?
Jim and I are going to drive up for the opening
if I can get out of that conference
I have in Sonoma with those massage therapists .
You know how that can be .
He doesn 't want your massage .
Do you , baby ?
Get back inside .
Don 't let me get cold .
This is really upsetting , okay ?
I 'm here to heal ,
but this is really ... This is upsetting !
- It 's upsetting ! - It 's not what you think .
No , no . It 's exactly what I think !
But you know what ? It 's your life .
- Vivian , please . - I ... Don 't . It 's your relationship , Evan .
( music playing )
Look , I 'm a DJ like Evan !
Why didn 't you let your girlfriend in ?
Are you ashamed of us ? Or are you fucking her , too ?
- Get out of my house ! - Be careful ,
these two cute little girls can put you behind bars
- for the rest of your life ! - Get out of my house !
What would your client say ? Your neighbors ?
What would your wife say if we told her everything we did last night ?
Get out !
( speaking Spanish )
It 's gonna be such a shame to see your wife divorce you !
And your business ruined
over a single night of perversion !
You wanna go door-to-door telling your neighbors you 're a child molester ?
What would the other parents do ?
Let their kids play here if you 're a convicted pedophile ?
There 's Evan !
I didn 't think you had it in you .
( groaning )
( panting )
911 , what 's your emergency ?
I 'd like to report a break-in .
You 're calling from 458 ...
Can you give us a ride ?
Let 's go .
( soft music playing on car radio )
( Genesis ) Well , this isn 't awkward at all .
Cool car , Evan .
( girls giggling )
This one on the right .
Out .
You 're not gonna get out and say bye ?
Go .
Don 't you want to come in and meet my mom ?
( speaking in Spanish )
- Oh ! - Bye !
Send our love to Karen and the kids !
Bye !
( rock music playing )
( glass breaking )
Hello ?
Oh , my God !
( Genesis humming )
( continues humming )
( Evan struggling )
( Evan ) Oh !
What the hell are you doing ?
( struggling )
Genesis , please , this is crazy , untie me !
( coughing )
What 's the point of this ?
I 'm a good person .
I made a mistake .
We can forget this ever happened .
Please ! Please !
Haven 't you ever made a mistake ?
- ( Genesis humming ) - ( Evan grunting )
( grunts )
( Bel ) Daddy !
Oh , Daddy !
Look what I found .
Oh , my God !
You take that off .
That 's my daughter 's . You take that off !
You like how it fits me , Daddy ?
- Look . - Take those off ,
you fucking crazy bitch !
Okay .
You know , every girl 's first love
is their daddy , huh ?
You 're sick .
You like what you see ?
Huh ? You like what you see ?
Daddy ?
( speaking in Spanish )
- Huh ? - No .
Bel .
Untie me .
Untie me , please .
If you really love me ,
untie me .
Ignore that asshole .
He 's not an asshole .
He 's my Daddy .
You don 't listen to her , Daddy .
She doesn 't love you the way I do .
I love you , Daddy .
I 've loved you ever since Mommy brought you home .
Remember that night when we were all alone
and you snuck into my room ?
And I pretended to be asleep .
But when you took off my clothes ,
I couldn 't pretend any longer .
We did things you and Mommy never did .
I hope you 're not angry at me anymore , Daddy .
I only did that to Mommy
because I wanted you all to myself .
Bel , Bel , untie me , please ?
Please .
You can tuck me in like you always did .
What 's wrong , Daddy ?
Huh ?
Don 't you want to fuck your little girl again ?
Did you forget what you did to me all those years ?
Why did you do that to me ?
Why did you do that to me !
- Bel ... - Why ?
Stop ! Bel !
( speaking in Spanish )
- Stop ! Bel ! - ( speaking in Spanish )
Bel , stop !
Why did you do that to me !
Why ! Why did you do that to me !
Stop ! Stop !
Bel ! Stop , please !
- ( slapping ) - ( Evan ) Stop it ! Stop it !
( Bel crying )
Shh .
Untie me .
What the fuck is that ?
( speaking in Spanish ) ( phone ringing )
You 're not hiding something , are you , Evan ?
What are you hiding here , huh ?
Come on , where is it , Daddy ?
It 's Karen on FaceTime !
- I 've been dying to meet her . - Answer it .
- Let 's get to know her . - No ! No !
You 're right , this could get awkward .
- What are you doing ? - Much better .
Don 't !
Can a cock answer an iPhone ?
Yes , Belly , but it 's gotta be hard .
Okay .
No ! Please !
- It could be my kids ! - Hi Evan , welcome back .
So ? Have they ever seen a cheating dick before ?
How about covered in her lipstick ?
Okay ! Okay , okay , okay , okay , okay , okay . Please .
Bel , I 'll do whatever you want .
Yes ! Yes !
Okay . Okay .
Now , fuck me , Daddy !
- Fuck me ! - Attaboy , Evan .
Fuck her .
Fuck her like it was last night .
- ( groaning ) - Yeah , fuck her good !
( moaning )
Fuck me , Daddy !
Fuck me like you fuck your little daughter !
( grunting and moaning )
Doggy style , Belly !
( barking )
You want something to eat , Bel ?
No , I 'm okay .
Okay .
( Bel crying out )
( barking )
Fuck me , Daddy !
Fuck me like you fuck Mommy !
( Bel groaning )
- ( moaning ) - Yeah , Daddy 's little girl !
( moaning and grunting )
You 're a good little girl !
( grunting )
- Fuck me , Daddy ! - Yeah !
Fuck me like you fuck Mommy !
( groaning )
Ow !
( squealing )
( shouting )
( groaning )
Arghh !
My scar ! My scar ! My scar !
My surgery !
You 've been a very bad boy , Evan !
Please , please , please take it out ! Take it out !
Oh , my God !
Oh , my
God !
Why did you hit me , Daddy ?
Now we have to punish you .
( grunts )
( music playing )
Welcome to America 's favorite game show ,
Who Wants to be a Pedophile !
Where we give the audience what they want !
The chance to punish a pedophile .
But first ,
let 's welcome our lovely , beautiful and charming ,
Ms. Bel !
( TV audience applauding )
Hello , Ms. Bel .
For tonight 's contestant ,
we have a very special one ,
he 's not only an architect but also a DJ ,
a husband , a father of two ,
possibly three .
Four .
All the way from one percent land ,
Mr. Evan Webber !
( applause )
Ms. Bel , would you please get our contestant ready ?
Sure .
You 're both crazy fucking bitches !
You look 21 , you lied to me !
Oh , like you lied to your wife ?
What I tell my wife is none of your goddamn ...
- ( music screeching ) - ( crying out )
God ! God !
Stop ! Stop ! Stop ! Stop ! My ears ! My ears !
I 'll go deaf ! I 'll go deaf !
This is fucking serious !
I could go deaf !
The game hasn 't started yet .
Our first category ...
Schoolyards .
How far away from school
will Evan have to pick up his kids ?
100 yards ?
500 yards ?
Or two miles ?
This is fucking sick !
( volume turned up )
Arghh !
( grunting )
Wrong answer . Correct answer is
you can 't pick up your kids from prison .
Fuck , fuck , fuck , fuck , fuck !
Please !
What 's our next category , Ms. Bel ?
I love this one .
Daddies .
Evan , this should be easy for you .
How many family men have survived this game ?
None .
What was that ?
Correct !
( TV audience applauds )
- Next question . - Genesis .
You 've proved your point .
( screaming )
God ! I can 't hear ! I can 't hear !
Please stop !
All you have to do is answer the question , Evan .
Okay .
Well , ask it , for fuck 's sake !
What 's the proper punishment for a pedophile ?
Is it prison where you get raped every day
and you never get to see your family again ?
Castration ?
Or death ?
Tick-tock . Tick-tock . Tick-tick-tock .
Tick-tock . Tick-tock . Tick-tock . Tick-tock .
Ten seconds .
( doorbell ringing )
Well , looks like it 's time for our first commercial break .
We 'll be back after a message from our sponsors .
Hello . It 's me , Louis !
Mr. Webber ?
( cell phone vibrating )
Who 's Louis ?
( knocking on door )
Fucking douche bag .
Get that sheet , cover him up .
( muffled yelling )
( coughing )
Shh !
- You must be Louis . - Yes .
I 'm Bernadette . I 'm Uncle Evan 's niece .
Oh , hi , nice to meet you .
Obviously , you 're with Uncle Evan .
Sorry , we 're shooting a music video .
Well , you guys picked an awesome location .
Come on in .
So where 'd you come in from ?
- Dallas . - Oh ? I used to live in Austin .
Oh , I 've never been .
Well , it 's fun when you 're in college .
Yeah , I went to Parsons .
Oh , great school . I went to SVA .
- Hi . - Hi .
- I 'm Louis . - Hi .
- Hi . I 'm ... - She 's Macarena .
- She 's my friend from Spain . - Oh . ( speaking in Spanish )
( speaking in Spanish )
- He 's here to pick up ... - The art work outside .
- Yes . - Excuse me .
- Somebody touch this ? - We didn 't touch it .
It 's Aunt Karen 's stuff , we wouldn 't go near it .
I did see Evan in here earlier ,
maybe he did .
Okay ,
' cause it 's not supposed to be like this .
It 's supposed to be bubble-wrapped and packed up and ready to go .
- Why would Evan do this ? - She said it wasn 't us .
Okay .
Oh , fuck .
Oh , my God .
What the fuck did y 'all do ?
What the fuck is this shit !
( breathing heavily )
We didn 't want to tell you , someone broke in
and that 's why Evan 's out .
- He was chasing them . - Yeah .
Shut the fuck up !
Shut the fuck up , both of you right now !
Nobody fucking move !
I 'm calling the cops right now .
Please don 't tell Karen .
This could be our little secret .
Bitch , you 're barking up the wrong fucking tree .
I 'm from Oakland , ho !
I know two ghetto ass hos when I see ' em !
Come to think of it , Evan doesn 't even have any fucking nieces .
( yelling ) Who the fuck are you ?
You better hope the police get here before Karen does .
( banging )
- What the fuck was that ? - Nothing .
- Hey , wait . - Wait .
- It 's nothing . - Get out of my way !
- Shit . - ( muffled grunts )
( muffled coughing )
Shit !
Mr. Webber !
Are you okay ? Oh , fuck !
They 're crazy !
Close the door . Close the door .
Louis !
Louis , no !
- I gotta stop these crazy ass bitches . - Louis , forget it !
They 're dangerous !
( screaming )
No ! No ! Stop !
Stop it !
What are you doing !
( gasping )
( gasping for breath )
( laughing )
Looking for this ?
Louis ! Be careful !
They 're crazy !
( Bel ) Monkey in the middle ! Monkey in the middle !
( Genesis We can 't say that , Belly , it 's racist .
Okay , man in the middle !
Give it to him !
No , Genesis , give him that !
( gasps and thuds )
Louis !
Genesis ! Please , this isn 't his fault ! Please call an ambulance , help him !
Fucker !
Bel , please help him !
Call an ambulance , I promise I won 't say anything !
Bel , Genesis ! Call an ambulance , for fuck 's sake !
I think it 's a little late for an ambulance , Evan .
He tripped , it 's his fault .
We were just playing monkey in the middle .
I mean , man in the middle .
Oh , my God !
( laughing hysterically )
You killed him !
Your wife killed him with her shitty sculpture .
This shit 's dangerous , Evan .
How can you keep this here with kids ?
That 's irresponsible parenting .
Yeah maybe your wife should stick to painting .
Get the fuck away from me !
Where do you think you 're going , Evan ?
Get the fuck off me ! Leave me alone !
Wanna go for a little ride ?
You can 't run away from us , Daddy .
You can 't escape .
( giggling )
Ahhh !
This is what happens when you break the rules of the game , Evan .
This is just like art class .
( Genesis ) What I did to Karen 's statue
is nothing compared to what I 'm going to do to you
if I ever see your fucking lying face again .
I trusted you both , how could you fuck my wife ?
Never come near my family again .
Disappear or you 're fucking dead .
( beeps )
( groans )
Which way is MOMA ?
( chuckling ) It 's more like " momma . "
Ronnie is gonna have a field day with this one .
Yeah , I 'm sure he will .
( Genesis ) That guy 's a magician .
Yeah .
( Genesis ) He can make anything disappear .
Let 's finish this .
( chair knocking )
Wow , those were some really long commercials .
Thanks to our sponsor Louis for that little lovely break .
Now ! Back to our million dollar question .
What is the proper punishment for a pedophile ?
Please .
I love my children . I love my wife .
I 'm a good father .
How can you judge anyone ?
You 're murderers .
Is that your final answer ?
Cause you 're gonna go deaf in about 10 seconds from now .
Please , Genesis !
I 'm a good father !
Until yesterday .
That doesn 't change how much I love them !
( coughs )
Do you really love them , Evan ?
Really ?
More than anything in the world .
So why didn 't you think of them when you were inside us ?
Yeah , why , Evan ?
Last night had nothing to do with my family .
Damn right it didn 't , Evan !
It had nothing to do with them .
Your family are victims .
Victims of your sleazy , disgusting , perverted behavior .
Jake . Lisa .
They don 't deserve a father like you .
This is what you did to your family .
You pervert .
( speaking Spanish )
Genesis , please , this isn 't the answer !
( imitates buzzer ) Wrong answer .
Correct answer is death .
We 'll be back after this commercial break .
Death ?
You 're gonna kill me ?
You 're gonna fucking kill me !
Why ? Why ! Because I fucked you ?
You fucked me ! You fucked me !
You came to my house ! You came to me !
I got you a car , I brought you your clothes ,
you took a fucking bubble bath !
You wanted it ! You wanted it ! You came on to me !
What was I supposed to do ?
You sucked my cock , you both fucking sucked my cock !
It was free pizza ! Free fucking pizza !
It just shows up at my fucking door !
What am I supposed to do ?
" We 're flight attendants . Come on , fuck us !
No one will know . Come on , fuck us ! "
Oh , twosomes , threesomes . It doesn 't matter !
Starfish ! Husbands ! You don 't give a fuck ,
you 'll just fuck anything , you 'll just fuck anything !
Well , you lied to me , I tried to help you !
I let you in ,
I was a good guy , I 'm a good father !
And you just fucking fucked me !
What ? Now , you 're gonna kill me !
You 're gonna kill me ? Why ?
Why ? ' Cause you fucked me ?
What the fuck-fuck-fuck , this is fucking insane !
You 're to be executed at dawn .
If I were you ,
I wouldn 't waste my last few hours crying about it .
( Bel ) I 'm sorry , Daddy .
It is the only way .
Bel ?
Oh , my God ! Oh , my God !
Oh , my God !
( Bel grunts with effort )
( grunts )
FaceTime . Karen !
FaceTime . Karen .
Digging a grave is fucking tiring .
- ( Bel ) And filthy . - ( phone ringing )
Your wife 's clothes are gonna need dry cleaning .
What 's that ?
( ringing continues )
You can 't have access to an iPad , Evan .
You could be trying to reach a child .
( Bel giggles )
Let 's face it , Evan . You 're a monster .
Or should I say ( mocking ) monster !
( growling )
What ?
Monster surprised ?
How do you know about that ?
Oh , monster confused !
How the fuck do you know that !
Monster will be quiet !
You spied on me ?
On my kids ?
Oh , my fucking God !
Oh , my fucking God ! Jesus !
I 'm so fucking stupid !
Yeah , you are .
( Bel snickering ) Monster retarded .
( mocking indistinctly )
( Genesis ) Let 's change , I feel gross .
Look at all this shit .
( groaning )
( Genesis ) This is you , Evan .
This is gonna be your little fucking head , you fucking cheater !
( groaning )
( Bel ) I love this color ! Red 's my favorite !
( girls grunting )
( squealing )
( snickering )
( Genesis ) Time for a haircut , Evan .
Gotta be pretty for your funeral .
( Bel ) He 's so hairy .
You don 't wanna lose an ear .
Hold still .
( Genesis ) There we go . You look pretty .
There 's Evan cutie !
There you have it .
Oh , now we see your pretty face .
Fucking bitches !
( mocking ) " I love the sound of vinyl . I 'm Evan . "
( Bel ) Watch this , Evan .
( moaning )
( grunting )
( cheering )
( gasps )
Jackpot !
Is that real ?
What a clever way to hide this from the kids , Evan !
You know , most firearm deaths are a family member of the gun owner .
( Bel ) I don 't own a gun .
It 's dangerous .
Untie him .
- Are you sure ? - Yeah .
Genesis , please don 't point that at me .
I know ,
it 's cheating . We still have 90 minutes .
But you were keeping secrets from us , Evan .
Had you gotten to this before us
I don 't think we 'd be having this conversation .
And you wouldn 't do the same ?
I 'm not like you , Evan .
I don 't own a gun , I don 't shoot people .
I sure as hell don 't bend the rules for my own convenience .
Untie him , Belly .
( winces )
I don 't want him to kick me .
( Genesis ) He won 't .
He kicks , I shoot .
He knows that .
Don 't you , Evan ?
What do you want ?
I wanna play hide and seek .
What ?
( sighs )
Thirty seconds . Only inside the house .
You leave the house , I shoot .
What 're you gonna do when you find me ?
Well , if we don 't find you by sunrise ,
we 'll leave .
- Bullshit . - Thirty seconds . Go ! Go !
( both ) Go ! ( Genesis ) Go !
( both ) 30 , 29 ...
28 , 27 ...
26 , 25 ...
24 , 23 , 22 ...
( Genesis ) Go !
Ready or not ? Here we come !
( both giggling )
Evan !
You can 't hide from us .
Here we come .
Evan ?
We can smell you , Evan .
Daddy ?
Psst ! In here .
- Evan ? - Oh , Evan ?
Are you here , monster ?
Evan ?
Shit !
Evan !
( Genesis ) Yeah , there he goes ! Stop !
Evan ! Stop !
Oh , fuck !
Don 't fucking move !
Help me ! Help me !
- Scream all you fucking want ! - Help me !
No one 's fucking home ! We tried every house !
( alarm ringing )
( Evan groaning )
( Genesis ) Are you ready !
( Evan ) Please don 't do this !
- ( Genesis ) Time to say goodbye ! - Please ! Please !
Help !
Help me !
Please , somebody help me !
Help ! Please somebody , help !
Please , let me go !
Help ! Please help me ! Somebody help me !
No ! Help me !
No ! No ! No ! No ! No !
No , help ! Help !
( both ) One , two , three !
( Genesis ) Whoopsie-daisy !
( grunts )
( Bel ) So Evan , did we hurt your shoulder ?
( Genesis ) We want you to be comfy , Evan .
( grunting and groaning )
Help ! Help !
Don 't move , Evan . You might get dirt in your eyes .
Yeah , close your eyes , baby .
Help ! Help !
Help !
Help ! Help ! Help !
Please . Please .
Please . Please , don 't do this .
Please ! Bel . Please .
It looks like he 's trying to communicate .
Please .
If you promise to behave , I 'll take out the gag .
Okay .
Don 't do this . Please ?
I 'll do whatever you want . I 'll do whatever you want .
Whatever !
Even calling your family and telling them everything you did to us ?
Yes .
Yes . Yes . Yes . I 'll tell them . I 'll tell them .
Okay , let 's give him a lifeline .
I love the lifeline part . Let 's see .
But the lifeline is a phone call .
Not FaceTime .
Your wife 's not gonna see you like this .
( on voicemail ) Hi , this is Karen Alvarado ,
please leave a message or send a text . Ciao .
( beeps )
Go ahead , talk .
Honey . I 'm sorry for what I 'm gonna tell you .
They made me .
Fuck !
Call 911 !
- Call 911 ! I 've been kidnapped ... - Evan , Evan ...
- ... by two girls ! - Evan !
Call 911 !
- Call 911 ! - No , no , no , Evan !
- You broke the rule . - Evan , why did you do that ?
Well , now she 'll fucking find you !
Not really .
I hung up as soon as it hit voice mail . I knew you 'd pussy out .
You fucking whores !
I 'll fucking kill you , you fucking-fuck bitch cunt !
I 'll fucking kill you ! You fucking bitches !
Oh , there 's Evan . There he is !
We missed you .
Fucking whores !
( growling )
Knock-knock !
I said knock-knock .
No !
I don 't think he can talk .
Okay . Knock-knock .
Who 's there ?
- Cheating Evan . - Cheating Evan who ?
Cheating " Evan-tually " gets you killed .
No ! No !
- Ready , Evan ? - No !
No !
- One ! - No !
- Two . - Do it !
- No ! No ! - Three !
( laughing )
Look at his face .
( Evan sobbing )
We got you good .
You didn 't really think we were gonna kill you , did you ?
We 're not animals .
It was just a game , Evan .
A game ? A game ?
You know what ?
For a moment , I thought you were the one who 'd say no .
And now we have to play a game with someone else .
You know what 's funny ? They never say no .
No matter who they are .
No matter how much they love their families .
You 're all the same .
Bye , Evan .
You were my favorite .
( Genesis ) Oh !
Wish me happy birthday . I turn 22 next week .
Yeah .
BEL : I freaked out when I turned 18 .
But you made me feel 15 again . Thanks , Evan .
( giggling )
Let 's get out of here .
Oh , I almost forgot . Yes , your phone .
You know you really should be more careful with Facebook .
If you don 't log out someone could do terrible things with it .
Post something really personal for all your friends to see .
Look closely . So you 'll remember us .
( Genesis , recorded ) Yes , Evan , fuck her !
( Bel ) Fuck me , Daddy !
( Evan ) Okay .
( Genesis ) Attaboy , Evan . Fuck her !
( Bel ) Fuck me ! Fuck me !
I 'm sure you 'll get a lot of likes though .
( Genesis ) Doggy style , Belly !
Enjoy !
( Bel Howling )
BEL : Oh !
Bye , Evan ! Muah ! We 'll miss you !
Oh !
No !
( moaning and crying out from phone )
Oh , no !
( music playing )
( groaning )
Fuck me , Daddy !
God , God !
( panting )
( grunts )
( Karen ) Take your bags to your rooms . Then go use the bathroom .
And then we 're gonna go see Monkey , okay ?
- Are you guys tired ? - ( Both ) Yeah !
( Lisa ) Monkey ?
Monkey ?
Daddy had a party .